The Emperor set the laptop
recovery time to 23:55 PM.
It's our best window to create
an opening for as long as possible.
We'll cut electricity supply at 23:55 PM
and invade the tower.
Operation will begin at... 23:30 PM!
Feint Operation!
Power Station Invasion Operation!
Commence Feint Operation and
Power Station Invasion Operation
Begin!
Both Team Feint and Team PS are on the move.
Huh? You can see Team PS too?
You sure we even need my Presentation Right?
I just happen to be able to
see their location for now.
I won't be able to see them through buildings.
Your Right will be our main lifeline.
By the way, how're things on your end?
Up and running, for real!
The side monitors display each team's
outgoing communication devices, right?
Yeah, their messages will show up here.
What about the two monitors in the middle?
The bottom one's for me
to send them messages.
I'll type messages in the notepad
For real
and display them on their
incoming communication devices.
For real
The same goes for the other way around,
so we can communicate back and forth.
Reply
What about the top monitor?
It's... for operation purposes.
T-minus goal time...
Tasuketsu: Fate of the Majority
Hibiya Park Yuraku Gate
- Koya Shimomura
- Shuji Nihonyanagi
Team Feint A, Koya Shimomura
and Shuji Nihonyanagi.
So they move if we get close,
and stop when we back off.
We can't get too far away.
Yeah, we gotta stay close
if we wanna lure them.
Hibiya Park Naka-Saiwai Gate
- Makoto Agatsuma
- Hikari Ebina
Team Feint B, Makoto
Agatsuma and Hikari Ebina.
Leading puppets from Naka-Saiwai Gate.
It's not too difficult. We just need
to stay calm and we'll be okay.
Yeah.
These two groups will
lure puppets in the park.
Oi Thermal Power Station
- Tojuro Yagihashi
Shinagawa
Thermal Power Station
- Kazuhiko Sato
- Eren Kunashiri
Team PS is also underway at the same time.
At exactly 23:55 PM, as the
Emperor recovers the laptop,
they'll cut power lines and
halt electricity supply.
Team Emperor, on standby at Kasumi Gate,
will enter the Emperor's tower.
Kasumi Gate
Puppets are on the move. Shimomura
Begin Operations! For real!
: Borinmaru Gokokuhotenji
Puppets are on the move. Shimomura
All good here. Agatsuma
Team Feint's moving without a hitch!
Looks like Team PS has
encountered puppets as well.
How do you do?
Since I won't be able to
greet the Emperor myself,
I suppose you'll have to bear my wrath...
as I avenge Sudo-kun!
No one gave you permission
to start yet, fool.
I still have time to cut the power.
No need to rush.
Now, here's a seemingly
normal black cloth...
Not quite as exciting
when this is your audience.
But now that I know that
you used my gift in your final act,
I have no choice but to return
the favor, my dear friend.
Welcome to my magic show, dedicated
to my friend and the loathsome Emperor.
Prepare yourself for a blast.
You all! Get out of my way!
Man, Senpai...
Your Compliance Right is no joke!
I mean it! It's "stupendular"!
You mean "stupendous" or "spectacular"?
Yeah, that! With your Compliance Right,
getting these puppets to cut
the power lines should be no sweat!
I gotta make it happen!
What?
Nothing, I was just thinking about
how you were such a scaredy-cat,
but now you're so brave!
Are you saying I can't grow up?!
I promised myself I won't run away anymore!
C'mon, let's go!
Roger that!
Out of my way!
My Compliance Right didn't work?
Does he have his own will?
Take my bucket special!
Hold him down and beat him up
until he can't move!
You heard her!
Now's our chance!
Yeah!
We made it!
What time is it?
Umm... 23:40 PM!
So we've got 15 minutes until
we need to cut the power lines.
Perfect. Keep it up. Come on...
Shimomura-san!
This puppet's not like the others!
It's like it has its own will...
like it's alive!
Shoot—
All good here. Agatsuma
Shimomura-san down. Nihonyanagi
Agatsuma dead. Ebina
Damn it! They got Shimomura and Agatsuma!
They've lured the puppets
far enough from the tower.
Tell the two who are left to evacuate!
Roger that!
Eren Senpai... Call me stupid, but...
What? Is it something bad?
Well, um...I don't see any
power lines here, do you?
Huh? Wait, what?
It may be here somewhere, but...
You've gotta be kidding!
We have less than 15 minutes left!
I guess we better look for them.
But how are we supposed to...
Wait! Let's contact Gobo using
the device he gave us!
He'll be able to tell us
where the power lines are!
You've got the outgoing device, right?
Hey, great call!
I forgot it at the coffee shop
when we were on standby...
What?! Are you stupid?!
What the hell are you doing?!
You're kidding, right?!
Let's see, how else can we contact him...
He designated separate devices for
outgoing and incoming communication.
There's no other way!
I have the incoming device, but
this is no good to send messages...
Senpai, could you go back and get it?
What?
You'll be safe with the Compliance Right.
You just need to go back the way we came.
When you find the device, contact Gobo.
I'll be here on standby
with the incoming device.
Just ask him to display
where the power lines are.
And I'll be there in a split!
But what are you gonna do until then?
I'll look for it on my own!
Who knows, I may even find them.
It took us over 10 minutes to get here,
so it'll be past 23:50 PM by the time
you get to the coffee shop.
You won't make it back in time,
so stay put there.
Just send me the message
and I'll take it from there!
But you don't have the Compliance Right
to send puppets to cut the power lines!
Look, I'll figure it out...
There's no other way.
Fine, I suppose I'll trust you.
Oh, just one more thing!
I'll give you my phone number.
You mean in case it works?
Thanks! Don't delete it by accident!
Unlike you, I won't make that mistake.
Anyways, don't be too reckless.
Tasuketsu: Fate of the Majority
Almost time...
Let's begin.
23:52 PM!
I made it... three more minutes...
I need to hurry and find that device.
Hang on, what?! Three minutes?!
How will he make it to the
power lines in three minutes?!
I've never had such a reactionless
audience. What a bore.
Now, if you'll come over
and join me on stage...
Man, I'm really stupid...
But those guys stuck it out
with an idiot like me.
They never gave up on me and
treated me as an equal through it all...
Even though I'm no good for anything.
Not just Sane. Eren Senpai, too.
They all trusted me.
Can't ask for much more than that.
How did I get so lucky?
Ippy-hiko! Here's
the location of the
power lines!
It's long but be
sure to look it over!
For real!
Oh good, Eren Senpai made it
to the coffee shop. That's a relief.
I finally got a girl to take my number!
Not that I can use it, but oh well.
A radius of 20 meters... This should be good.
I wonder, Sane... if you realized
what I was hiding from you?
Or did I do a good job at masking it?
I figured if I'm gonna be useless...
I might as well play the part
of the happy old me!
That way, if you're ever down, you can
talk to me and go back to the good days.
And now that I've gained this power...
I'll make it count.
At least this once, at the end of the road.
Prime
Right
Prime Right Access Denied
You are not permitted to
acquire a Prime Right.
Prime
Right
I'll smile believing in our victory.
You better win!
You all can cut the power lines for me.
Catch ya later, Saneatsu. Everyone.
Prime Right under
the Production Attribute...
Explosion Right!
The power's out!
They did it!
Laptop recovery confirmed!
Kazuhiko?
Al right! Souma, let's go!
Yeah!
Agatsuma dead. Ebina
Entering the Emperor's tower. Jin
Commence invasion of the Emperor's tower!
Commence Invasion of Emperor's Tower
Prime Right of Materialization!
After the puppets are lured away,
Team Emperor draws in on the tower.
So that's... the Emperor's tower!
Souma! Rika! You two keep the puppets away!
Roger that!
You won't have to worry about getting
shot down as long as you're with me.
Don't get too rash!
Same to you!
The tower may be equipped with
an in-house power generator,
but we won't be noticed
while the power's down.
The longer the Emperor takes to react,
the greater our advantage.
Wanna block routes connecting lower levels?
Yeah!
Fuse!
Ryuta! The stairs are over here!
Got it!
Fuse!
There!
We're clear of any
connecting routes over here!
Clear here too!
Let's go!
They're here, just as we thought...
Saaya, time?
23:55:40 PM.
The puppets really are corpses.
They don't bleed when cut.
Right.
Let's go!
We can make it!
They're here, too?!
It's fine, we'll force our way through!
Ryuta, follow us and protect Omi!
Can you clear the path with me, Saaya?
Sure!
Nice! Way to go!
There's the stairs!
As I thought... intruders.
It talked?!
Is it not a puppet?!
Ya gonna shoot me?!
Yes...
I reject!
It's... not bleeding.
But it looks just like a living human...
I guess the servants are
much more well-made...
The power!
It's still only 23:57 PM!
We can still make it!
Y-Yeah!
Does this mean... we can't
get in without a password?
Damn it... The doors seem to be thick steel.
It's too thick for even Ryuta
to break down instantly.
Should I try to break the pass code?
No, there could be an entry limit...
We have less than a minute left...
What now?!
By exercising the combined power
of multiple Prime Rights,
I have extended one minute to ten minutes.
Emperor?!
If you agree to negotiations,
you will be granted access.
However, this will involve exercising
the Prime Right of Negotiation.
By rule, all negotiation results will be
absolute, and resistance will be futile.
Do you wish to proceed?
You will renounce your Parental
Authority in return for access.
Yes or no?
So that's it!
The Emperor's tactic against
Parental Authority...
It was to make me renounce it
with their Negotiation Right!
No wonder they wanted
to lure me to them...
If I agree, I won't be able to
use Parental Authority.
But if I refuse, I won't be able
to meet the Emperor.
Still...
Fine, I agree! I renounce
my Parental Authority!
Negotiation complete.
I will now open the door.
Ryuta, the doors are opening. Ready?
Yeah, I'm all set. Whenever they're ready.
Thanks, Ryuta...
I'm always the one
putting you in a tight spot.
And now... I've lost my only power.
Don't sweat it. We're best friends, remember?
Besides, I'm happy with this.
So... that's what you look like.
You seem a lot younger in person.
Nice to meet you, Dad.
Or... I guess you're not anymore.
Then how about...
Nice to meet you.
Emperor
I'm the Emperor.